mostpopulararticles.com 2013-10-26

# United Kingdom, Europe - Most Popular Articles Online Classifieds

Mr. Lister Online  
PRIVACY DISCLOSURES

Information Collection & Use Registration

In order to use this Web site, you must first complete the registration form [and/or create a user name and password. During registration you are required to give contact information (such as name and email address). We use this information to contact you about the services on our site in which you have expressed interest. 

You have the option to provide demographic information (such as income level and gender) to us; we encourage you to submit this information so we can provide you a more personalized experience on our site. 

Member will be able to receive Resume/and/or Job Reports 

Cutting Edge Enterprises, LLC is the sole owner of the information collected on mrlisteronline.com or sellandtellrealestate.com. Cutting Edge Enterprises, LLC collects personally identifiable information from our users at several different points on our Web site. 

Orders  
If you purchase a product or service from us, we request certain personally identifiable information from you on our order form. You must provide contact information (such as name, email, and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date). 

We use this information for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you. 

Tell-A-Friend  
If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend�s name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. Cutting Edge Enterprises, LLC stores does not store this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program. 

Your friend may contact us at mrlisteronline.com or sellandtellrealestate.com to request that we remove this information from our database. 

Uses of Information  
All information collected for posting resumes, or posting jobs is not used for any other purposes, other than communication between candidate and employer. 

Communications from the Site 

Newsletters  
If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter, we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you. Out of respect for your privacy, we provide you a way to unsubscribe. Please see the �Choice and Opt-out� section. 

Service-related Announcements  
We will send you strictly service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email. 

Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account. 

Customer Service  
Based upon the personally identifiable information you provide us, we will send you a welcoming email to verify your username and password. We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request, and to manage your account. We will communicate with you by email or telephone, in accordance with your wishes. 

Profile   
We store information that we collect through cookies, log files, clear gifs to create a �profile� of your preferences. We tie your personally identifiable information, and [or] your purchasing history, to information in the profile, in order to provide tailored promotions and marketing offers and to improve the content of the site for you. 

We do not share your profile with other third parties. We share your profile in aggregate form only. 

Information Sharing and Disclosure 

Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)  
We share aggregated demographic information about our user base with our partners and advertisers. This information does not identify individual users. This data is only shared with possible employers, searching for candidates. 

We do not link aggregate user data with personally identifiable information. 

Personally identifiable information: 

We DO NOT Share Personally Identifiable Information with Third Parties 

Choice/Opt-out  
Through our secured web control panel, we provide you the opportunity to �opt-out� of having your personally identifiable information used for certain purposes, when we ask for this information. For example, if you purchase a product/service but do not wish to receive any additional marketing material from us, you can indicate your preference on our order form. 

If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication or by emailing us at mrlister@mrlisteronline.com. We offer an opportunity to opt-out of certain communications on our, or you may contact us at ONE] mrlister@mrlisteronline.comor to opt-out. 

You will be notified when your personal information is collected by any third party that is not our agent/service provider, so you can make an informed choice as to whether or not to share your information with that party. 

Log Files  
As is true of most Web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. 

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users� movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. 

We do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information. 

Cookies  
A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user�s computer for record-keeping purposes. We do not use cookies on this site. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site.. 

We use session ID cookies and/or persistent cookies. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site.. A session ID cookie expires when you close you browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser�s �help� file. 

Some of our business partners (e.g., advertisers) use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies. See �Third Party Advertisers.� 

This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by mrlisteronline.com only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. 

Links to Other Sites  
This Web site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by Cutting Edge Enterprises, LLC. Please be aware that we, Cutting Edge Enterprises, LLC, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. 

We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. 

This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this Web site. 

Access to Personally Identifiable Information 

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, delete or deactivate it by making the change on our member information page . 

Security  
The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). 

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can send email us at mrlister@mrlisteronline.com 

Business Transitions  
In the event Cutting Edge Enterprises, LLC goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via email of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information. 

Changes in this Privacy Statement  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page. 

Contact Us   
If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at: Cutting Edge Enterprises, LLC, 13790 SW Peninsula Dr. , Terrebonne, OR. 97760. Email: mrlister@mrlisteronline.com .
